Double-click to open the Printed Files folder.
Find the F Adding Plates in Scene Details.
Double-click on Knife Plates.
Or drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
Enter the window and double-click on the name of the Aorta file.
Enter Fibonacci and drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
Enter the Fibonacci and drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
Enter the Fibonacci and drag it to the 2D window.
Also, drag it to the 3D window.
Lock a line of the Flare from the Flare tool.
Lock a line of the Flare tool.
In the 2D tool bar, select the Center Blur Tool.
Select all the foundation lines from the 2D window.
Set the base line to the inner line.
Select the 5th of the 2D full-fledged blueprints.
Click to lock the panel outline.
Unlock the panel outline.
In the 2D tool, select the fold and fold tool.
Set the fold and fold direction.
Click the 2D window next to the skirt panel and move the mouse.
The arrow follows the light.
It means that the fold will be folded.
Pass the arrow through the entire skirt panel.
Double-click to complete the setting direction.
When the fold and fold buttons pop out of the window,
select Follow and then click OK.
Repeat this operation on the back of the skirt panel.
In the 2D tool bar, select the fold and fold tool.
Fold the button.
Start folding through a section of the belt of the single button.
Then press again when the shelf is finished.
This is the first half of the fold.
The second part of the fold, the seven points of the single button菷
Select else from the boxes at the end of the shelf
Then press again when the details are completed.
Make sure the fold and fold are aligned
and follow the thickening direction of the fold.
Use thereturn to countdown if necessary.
Use the Line Selection tool to divide the panels into sections.
Select the 4th panel of the 3D vertical tool bar.
Click on the display point.
The blue point will be displayed around the 3D window virtual model.
Select all panels in the 2D window.
Press Ctrl A to select all panels.
Move the panels up and down.
Enter the blocked point.
Arrange the panels around the model.
Adjust the position of the panels in the purple bar arranged by the virtual machine.
Select the mouse to the 4th panel of the 3D vertical tool bar.
Click on the display point.
Hide the display point.
Select the 1 panel in the 2D window.
In the virtual machine, select the 1 panel.
Paste the 1 panel.
In the 2D window, press Shift to select the front and back panels.
In the 3D window, right-click on the panel.
Select Harden on the menu.
Harden is to temporarily increase the hardness of the panel.
You can also fold it.
Activate the model.
The panel will be folded quickly.
When the folding model is completed,
Unhaze the skirt panels.
To unhaze the panels, select all panels.
The touch icon is a bit single.
Drag it to the menu.
Select the Unhaze panel.
Activate the model.
You can see the strength of the skirt.